Well, good morning.  So if we talk about numbers,
life
insurance companies have had very strong
premium collection numbers in the month of October.  And I would like to
specifically mention
one name in this which is SBI Life Insurance.
This is the second straight month where the company has
registered a very strong growth.
As I said, this is the second straight month
and this strong growth that has come in October has
come on a strong base.  That is,
a very strong growth company did it in October last year as well.
He has
built on strong growth and is
back to deliver a strong October 2025.  Let
me talk about specific numbers.
SBI Life's new business premium has
increased by 20%.  APE i.e. Annualized
Premium Equivalent has increased by 19%.
Retail APE also showed us growing at 19%.   This
means that group business has also increased and retail
business has also been seen growing very fast.
After this, the next number comes to Axis Max Le
Insurance, which is a listed entity
of Max Financial Services.  They have also seen very
strong growth and this has
come on a strong base.  New Business Premium has
increased by 15%.  APE increased by 17%.  Retail
AP grew by 16%.  HDFC Life
is a mixed growth company.
New business premiums increased by just 1% on a strong base.
APE increased by 7% and retail APE by 9%.
ICICI PDL Life is their growth week.  But
this one seems to be coming on a strong base.  New
business premium increased by 7%.  APE has increased by 9%
and retail APE has increased by 3%.
Finally, LIC has seen a very strong growth but on a
weak base, that is, strong growth has come on a favourable base.
New business premium has increased by 13%.
APE has increased by 30%.  Retail APE
increased by 28%.  Star of the Month for LIC
i.e. October month is SBI Life
Insurance without a doubt.
Definitely.  so good